{
    "subject": "Maud_of_Savoy",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Afonso_I_of_Portugal",
    "human_readable": "Maud of Savoy is married to Afonso I of Portugal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9388309717178345,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Maud of Savoy and Afonso I of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371617436408997,
            "question": "Is Maud of Savoy married to a Portuguese ruler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9181795716285706,
            "question": "To whom is Maud of Savoy married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9140558838844299,
            "question": "Who is married to Afonso I of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800120949745178,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Afonso I of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8028274178504944,
            "question": "What is the name of Afonso I of Portugal's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7777988910675049,
            "question": "Can you name a queen who was married to Afonso I of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6573594808578491,
            "question": "Is there a historical connection between Maud of Savoy and Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274844169616699,
            "question": "What is Maud of Savoy known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3132416605949402,
            "question": "Who held the title of Queen consort during Afonso I's reign?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maud of Savoy is married to Afonso I of Portugal.",
            "html": "yago_25145_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Maud of Savoy known for?",
            "html": "yago_25145_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a historical connection between Maud of Savoy and Portugal?",
            "html": "yago_25145_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a queen who was married to Afonso I of Portugal?",
            "html": "yago_25145_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25145_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25145/re-ranker-msmarco/79.txt and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25145/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt mention that Maud of Savoy was the wife of Afonso I King of Portugal, and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25145/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt provides further confirmation by listing their marriage as an event."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Maud of Savoy was married to Afonso I King of Portugal before June 1146 in Chamb\u00e9ry, Savoie, France. This confirms the marital relationship between Maud of Savoy and Afonso I of Portugal as described in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}